

I am very inqusitive to learning new skills convert into latest technologies.

CONTACT



Shalimar Scheme LAHORE



alirzaa911@gmail.com



freelancer.com.bd/u/alirzaa

ABOUT ME

Self-motivated Web Developer with 1+ years of experience. On a perpetual quest to continuously, evolve into something better. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects. Ambitious problem-solving Web Developer leveraging powerful set of technology skills. Eager to work with personnel in all areas of company to help boost profits and improve opportunities.



EXPERIENCE

HANDYBUILDS.COM

Full stack developer (Feb 2020 - Current)

- Developed Laravel and Vue js based application from scratch and integrate it with different Apis.
- Customize wordpress website and transfer it from one hosting to another hosting.
- Converted design assets into component-based HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Designed mobile friendly websites.
- Designed robust blogs, corporate and e-commerce websites, using platforms e.g Wordpress

FANTECHTIC.COM

PHP Web Developer (Jan 2017 - Feb 2019 part time)

- Wrote server-side and client-side code for projects using PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript, specifically with jquery framework.
- Designed mobile friendly websites.
- Leveraged strong understanding of WordPress to manipulate admin and theme components.
- Integrated several different APIs such as Finnhub and Alphavantage to framework.
- Work with multicultural and diverse team to create application for clients.
- Worked closely with Project Managers and other developers to define strategy.



SKILLS

CORE SKILLS

PROJECT SKILLS

Psd to html

Psd to wordpress

E-commerce

WP theme development

WP plugin development

Crud application

Shopify

API integaration

Dashboard and reports



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

2016 - 2020

JAVA

COMSATS university, Islamabad Lahore campus.

FSC PRE ENGINNERING

2013 - 2015

SHALIMAR college Baghbanpura Lahore.



FYP AND LEARNING

- Stock prediction system
- Machine Learning
- Deep learning

- Web based portal
- Graphs
- Integarations